The continuous sound from the TV
Piled up laundry - gotta do the wash today
Make a point of not going out, even if it's sunny
Make a toast with unspectacular snacks and alcohol
The two of us, though our sweets and bitters of life
May not mesh
As if to lean on each other
Let's shift things a little
The sun that you gave to me
So that it remains unhidden by the sun
I sing a melody to sustain the shine
Playful, slowly flowing day
Beyond I love you's
We're so alike, and I hope we'll
Continue laughing together until we grow old
Without you, it's a lonely, lonely day
In a dream, fall asleep in bed.
I'll wake you up with a morning call
I'll protect you from nightmares, Baby
By tracing footsteps that were left behind
I caught you off guard and hugged you from behind
I almost forget when it becomes repetitious
But looking back, I realize there was nothing ordinary about those days
The two of us with matching cells
The intertwining of the exceptional
Is what I want to savor in life, I realized in an afternoon of slumber
Sighs, escaping body heat
Not wanting to miss a single detail
I burn these sweet moments into memory
Playful, slowly flowing day
Beyond I love you's
We're so different, but I hope we'll
Continue laughing together until we grow old
Without you, it's a lonely, lonely day
In a dream, fall asleep in bed.
I'll wake you up with a morning call
I'll protect you from nightmares, Baby
Don't let go of our hands held together
Sorry, I guess I just want to be near you
The feelings kept in our hearts are mutual
See, we're even
Misunderstandings and mistakes are common
An approach that failed to go as planned, even sadness
Let's split them into two
Hoping it's not an ending
Trying to avoid being self-satisfied, avoid
Without you, right now, I'd be somewhere
Still unable to move
I want to say thank you
From now on, I'll be the one to support you
It's absurd how much
My love grows day by day
But when I face you, I just can't
Show you the way I really feel, I'm so sorry
Playful, slowly flowing day
Beyond I love you's
We're so alike, and I hope we'll
Continue laughing together until we grow old
Without you, it's a lonely, lonely day
In a dream, fall asleep in bed.
I'll wake you up with a morning call
I'll protect you from nightmares, baby